2023-09-02 04:23:04 INFO - Scenario 'Font settings: Check of text theme' start 2023-09-02 04:23:04 INFO - Setting application driver using the server on 'https://hub-cloud.browserstack.com/wd/hub' 2023-09-02 04:23:29 INFO - Application on platform 'ANDROID' is ready... 2023-09-02 04:23:29 INFO - Session id - e35f78874c2051f7b8e3c27c7189744d036a2bd2 2023-09-02 04:23:29 INFO - Step 0 - Close tutorial screen 2023-09-02 04:23:29 INFO - Button 'btnCloseTutorial' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 04:23:31 INFO - Step 1 - Welcome screen is opened 2023-09-02 04:23:32 INFO - Step 2 - Close welcome screen 2023-09-02 04:23:32 INFO - Button 'btnFindLibrary' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 04:23:32 INFO - Step 3 - Add library screen is opened 2023-09-02 04:23:33 INFO - Step 4 - Add library "LYRASIS Reads" on Add library screen 2023-09-02 04:23:34 INFO - Button 'Search' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 04:23:34 INFO - Text Field 'Search' :: Clearing 2023-09-02 04:23:34 INFO - Text Field 'Search' :: Typing 'LYRASIS Reads' 2023-09-02 04:23:38 INFO - Button 'LYRASIS Reads' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 04:23:38 INFO - Step 5 - Account "LYRASIS Reads" is present on Accounts screen 2023-09-02 04:23:38 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 04:23:41 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 04:23:41 INFO - Button 'Accounts' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 04:23:43 INFO - Step 6 - Enter credentials for 'LYRASIS Reads' account 2023-09-02 04:23:43 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 04:23:45 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 04:23:45 INFO - Button 'Accounts' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 04:23:46 INFO - Button 'LYRASIS Reads' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 04:23:47 INFO - Locking credential with barcode 01230000000002 2023-09-02 04:23:47 INFO - There are books on the account: 2023-09-02 04:23:48 INFO - bookName: The Black Kids Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-02 04:23:48 INFO - bookName: The Story of Nano Nagle Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-02 04:23:48 INFO - bookName: The Innovators Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-02 04:23:48 INFO - Books without revoke in link. BookName: Unprotected Distributor: framework.utilities.returningBooksUtil.Distributor@11794046 2023-09-02 04:23:48 INFO - Books without revoke in link. BookName: Chocolate Cream Pie Murder Distributor: framework.utilities.returningBooksUtil.Distributor@42f710d6 2023-09-02 04:23:48 INFO - bookName: Phantom Lover Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-02 04:23:48 INFO - bookName: Snow Crash Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-02 04:23:48 INFO - Count of books on the account after opening account: 5 2023-09-02 04:23:48 INFO - Text Field 'Card' :: Clearing 2023-09-02 04:23:48 INFO - Text Field 'Card' :: Typing '01230000000002' 2023-09-02 04:23:49 INFO - Text Field 'Pin' :: Clearing 2023-09-02 04:23:49 INFO - Text Field 'Pin' :: Typing '********' 2023-09-02 04:23:50 INFO - Button 'Log in' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 04:23:55 INFO - Button 'Log ... action' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-02 04:23:56 INFO - Step 7 - Login is performed successfully 2023-09-02 04:24:16 INFO - Button 'Log ... action' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-02 04:24:16 INFO - Step 8 - Open Catalog 2023-09-02 04:24:17 INFO - Button 'tabCatalog' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 04:24:37 INFO - Step 9 - Open search modal 2023-09-02 04:24:57 INFO - Button 'Search' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 04:24:59 INFO - Step 10 - Search 'available' book of distributor 'Palace Marketplace' and bookType 'EBOOK' from "LYRASIS Reads" and save as 'bookNameInfo' 2023-09-02 04:24:59 INFO - Count of attempts to get random book name without bad symbols-1 2023-09-02 04:24:59 INFO - randomBookName: The Three Little Men in the Forest 2023-09-02 04:24:59 INFO - Error details button is not present 2023-09-02 04:24:59 INFO - Text Field 'Search value input' :: Sending keys 'The Three Little Men in the Forest' 2023-09-02 04:25:01 INFO - Error details button is not present 2023-09-02 04:25:03 INFO - Step 11 - Click GET action button on EBOOK book with 'bookNameInfo' bookName on catalog books screen and save book as 'bookInfo' 2023-09-02 04:25:05 INFO - Label 'lblAuthor' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-02 04:25:05 INFO - Button 'actionButton' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 04:25:11 INFO - Step 12 - Open EBOOK book with READ action button and 'bookNameInfo' bookName on catalog books screen and save book as 'bookInfo' 2023-09-02 04:25:12 INFO - Label 'lblAuthor' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-02 04:25:12 INFO - Label 'lblBookName' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 04:25:12 INFO - Step 13 - Click READ action button on book details screen 2023-09-02 04:25:13 INFO - Button 'Read' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 04:25:13 INFO - Step 14 - Scroll page forward from 7 to 9 times 2023-09-02 04:25:13 INFO - Scrolling 7 times on reader epub screen 2023-09-02 04:25:29 INFO - Step 15 - Open font settings 2023-09-02 04:25:30 INFO - Button 'btnFontSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 04:25:30 INFO - Step 16 - Change contrast to BLACK_TEXT_ON_WHITE 2023-09-02 04:25:30 INFO - Button 'setThemeLight' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 04:25:31 INFO - Step 17 - The BLACK_TEXT_ON_WHITE background is correct 2023-09-02 04:25:31 INFO - context - NATIVE_APP 2023-09-02 04:25:31 INFO - context - WEBVIEW_org.thepalaceproject.palace 2023-09-02 04:25:32 INFO - pageSourceWithSettingsStart+++++++++++++++++++++++++ 2023-09-02 04:25:32 INFO -

The Three Little Men in the Forest

There was once a man whose wife died, and a woman whose husband died, and the man had a daughter, and the woman also had a daughter. The girls were acquainted with each other, and went out walking together, and afterwards came to the woman in her house. Then said she to the man’s daughter, “Listen, tell thy father that I would like to marry him, and then thou shalt wash thyself in milk every morning, and drink wine, but my own daughter shall wash herself in water and drink water.” The girl went home, and told her father what the woman had said. The man said, “What shall I do? Marriage is a joy and also a torment.” At length as he could come to no decision, he pulled off his boot, and said, “Take this boot, it has a hole in the sole of it. Go with it up to the loft, hang it on the big nail, and then pour water into it. If it hold the water, then I will again take a wife, but if it run through, I will not.” The girl did as she was ordered, but the water drew the hole together, and the boot became full to the top. She informed her father how it had turned out. Then he himself went up, and when he saw that she was right, he went to the widow and wooed her, and the wedding was celebrated.

The next morning, when the two girls got up, there stood before the man’s daughter milk for her to wash in and wine for her to drink, but before the woman’s daughter stood water to wash herself with and water for drinking. On the second morning, stood water for washing and water for drinking before the man’s daughter as well as before the woman’s daughter. And on the third morning stood water for washing and water for drinking before the man’s daughter, and milk for washing and wine for drinking, before the woman’s daughter, and so it continued. The woman became bitterly unkind to her step-daughter, and day by day did her best to treat her still worse. She was also envious because her step-daughter was beautiful and lovable, and her own daughter ugly and repulsive.

Once, in winter, when everything was frozen as hard as a stone, and hill and vale lay covered with snow, the woman made a frock of paper, called her step-daughter, and said, “Here, put on this dress and go out into the wood, and fetch me a little basketful of strawberries,—I have a fancy for some.” “Good heavens!” said the girl, “no strawberries grow in winter! The ground is frozen, and besides the snow has covered everything. And why am I to go in this paper frock? It is so cold outside that one’s very breath freezes! The wind will blow through the frock, and the thorns will tear it off my body.” “Wilt thou contradict me again?” said the stepmother, “See that thou goest, and do not show thy face again until thou hast the basketful of strawberries!” Then she gave her a little piece of hard bread, and said, “This will last thee the day,” and thought, “Thou wilt die of cold and hunger outside, and wilt never be seen again by me.”

Then the maiden was obedient, and put on the paper frock, and went out with the basket. Far and wide there was nothing but snow, and not a green blade to be seen. When she got into the wood she saw a small house out of which peeped three dwarfs. She wished them good day, and knocked modestly at the door. They cried, “Come in,” and she entered the room and seated herself on the bench by the stove, where she began to warm herself and eat her breakfast. The elves said, “Give us, too, some of it.” “Willingly,” she said, and divided her bit of bread in two and gave them the half. They asked, “What dost thou here in the forest in the winter time, in thy thin dress?” “Ah,” she answered, “I am to look for a basketful of strawberries, and am not to go home until I can take them with me.” When she had eaten her bread, they gave her a broom and said, “Sweep away the snow at the back door with it.” But when she was outside, the three little men said to each other, “What shall we give her as she is so good, and has shared her bread with us?” Then said the first, “My gift is, that she shall every day grow more beautiful.” The second said, “My gift is, that gold pieces shall fall out of her mouth every time she speaks.” The third said, “My gift is, that a king shall come and take her to wife.”

The girl, however, did as the little men had bidden her, swept away the snow behind the little house with the broom, and what did she find but real ripe strawberries, which came up quite dark-red out of the snow! In her joy she hastily gathered her basket full, thanked the little men, shook hands with each of them, and ran home to take her step-mother what she had longed for so much. When she went in and said good-evening, a piece of gold at once fell from her mouth. Thereupon she related what had happened to her in the wood, but with every word she spoke, gold pieces fell from her mouth, until very soon the whole room was covered with them. “Now look at her arrogance,” cried the step-sister, “to throw about gold in that way!” but she was secretly envious of it, and wanted to go into the forest also to seek strawberries. The mother said, “No, my dear little daughter, it is too cold, thou mightest die of cold.” However, as her daughter let her have no peace, the mother at last yielded, made her a magnificent dress of fur, which she was obliged to put on, and gave her bread-and-butter and cake with her.

The girl went into the forest and straight up to the little house. The three little elves peeped out again, but she did not greet them, and without looking round at them and without speaking to them, she went awkwardly into the room, seated herself by the stove, and began to eat her bread-and-butter and cake. “Give us some of it,” cried the little men; but she replied, “There is not enough for myself, so how can I give it away to other people?” When she had done eating, they said, “There is a broom for thee, sweep all clean for us outside by the back-door.” “Humph! Sweep for yourselves,” she answered, “I am not your servant.” When she saw that they were not going to give her anything, she went out by the door. Then the little men said to each other, “What shall we give her as she is so naughty, and has a wicked envious heart, that will never let her do a good turn to any one?” The first said, “I grant that she may grow uglier every day.” The second said, “I grant that at every word she says, a toad shall spring out of her mouth.” The third said, “I grant that she may die a miserable death.” The maiden looked for strawberries outside, but as she found none, she went angrily home. And when she opened her mouth, and was about to tell her mother what had happened to her in the wood, with every word she said, a toad sprang out of her mouth, so that every one was seized with horror of her.

Then the step-mother was still more enraged, and thought of nothing but how to do every possible injury to the man’s daughter, whose beauty, however, grew daily greater. At length she took a cauldron, set it on the fire, and boiled yarn in it. When it was boiled, she flung it on the poor girl’s shoulder, and gave her an axe in order that she might go on the frozen river, cut a hole in the ice, and rinse the yarn. She was obedient, went thither and cut a hole in the ice; and while she was in the midst of her cutting, a splendid carriage came driving up, in which sat the King. The carriage stopped, and the King asked,”My child, who are thou, and what art thou doing here?” “I am a poor girl, and I am rinsing yarn.” Then the King felt compassion, and when he saw that she was so very beautiful, he said to her, “Wilt thou go away with me?” “Ah, yes, with all my heart,” she answered, for she was glad to get away from the mother and sister.

So she got into the carriage and drove away with the King, and when they arrived at his palace, the wedding was celebrated with great pomp, as the little men had granted to the maiden. When a year was over, the young Queen bore a son, and as the step-mother had heard of her great good-fortune, she came with her daughter to the palace and pretended that she wanted to pay her a visit. Once, however, when the King had gone out, and no one else was present, the wicked woman seized the Queen by the head, and her daughter seized her by the feet, and they lifted her out of the bed, and threw her out of the window into the stream which flowed by. Then the ugly daughter laid herself in the bed, and the old woman covered her up over her head. When the King came home again and wanted to speak to his wife, the old woman cried, “Hush, hush, that can’t be now, she is lying in a violent perspiration; you must let her rest to-day.” The King suspected no evil, and did not come back again till next morning; and as he talked with his wife and she answered him, with every word a toad leaped out, whereas formerly a piece of gold had fallen out. Then he asked what that could be, but the old woman said that she had got that from the violent perspiration, and would soon lose it again. During the night, however, the scullion saw a duck come swimming up the gutter, and it said,

“King, what art thou doing now?

Sleepest thou, or wakest thou?”

And as he returned no answer, it said,

“And my guests, What may they do?”

The scullion said,

“They are sleeping soundly, too.”

Then it asked again,

“What does little baby mine?”

He answered,

“Sleepeth in her cradle fine.”

Then she went upstairs in the form of the Queen, nursed the baby, shook up its little bed, covered it over, and then swam away again down the gutter in the shape of a duck. She came thus for two nights; on the third, she said to the scullion, “Go and tell the King to take his sword and swing it three times over me on the threshold.” Then the scullion ran and told this to the King, who came with his sword and swung it thrice over the spirit, and at the third time, his wife stood before him strong, living, and healthy as she had been before. Thereupon the King was full of great joy, but he kept the Queen hidden in a chamber until the Sunday, when the baby was to be christened. And when it was christened he said, “What does a person deserve who drags another out of bed and throws him in the water?” “The wretch deserves nothing better,” answered the old woman, “than to be taken and put in a barrel stuck full of nails, and rolled down hill into the water.” “Then,” said the King, “Thou hast pronounced thine own sentence;” and he ordered such a barrel to be brought, and the old woman to be put into it with her daughter, and then the top was hammered on, and the barrel rolled down hill until it went into the river.

2023-09-02 04:25:32 INFO - pageSourceWithSettingsEnd+++++++++++++++++++++++++ 2023-09-02 04:25:33 INFO - Taking screenshot 2023-09-02 04:25:34 INFO - Test finished - logging out 2023-09-02 04:25:35 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 04:25:39 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 04:25:40 INFO - Button 'Accounts' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 04:25:41 INFO - Button 'LYRASIS Reads' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 04:25:42 INFO - Text Field 'Card' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-02 04:25:42 INFO - Text Field 'Pin' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-02 04:25:43 INFO - Button 'Log out' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 04:26:03 INFO - Button 'Log in' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-02 04:26:03 INFO - Unlocking credential for current thread 2023-09-02 04:26:03 INFO - isLoggerNullAfterAnnotation-framework.utilities.Logger@1684cb30

2023-09-02 03:46:06 INFO - Scenario 'Font settings: Check of increasing and reducing the text size' start 2023-09-02 03:46:06 INFO - Setting application driver using the server on 'https://hub-cloud.browserstack.com/wd/hub' 2023-09-02 03:46:31 INFO - Application on platform 'ANDROID' is ready... 2023-09-02 03:46:31 INFO - Session id - 8ff62cb9d42abe7f14678e9585c88248f32e3953 2023-09-02 03:46:31 INFO - Step 0 - Close tutorial screen 2023-09-02 03:46:31 INFO - Button 'btnCloseTutorial' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 03:46:34 INFO - Step 1 - Welcome screen is opened 2023-09-02 03:46:34 INFO - Step 2 - Close welcome screen 2023-09-02 03:46:34 INFO - Button 'btnFindLibrary' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 03:46:34 INFO - Step 3 - Add library screen is opened 2023-09-02 03:46:35 INFO - Step 4 - Add library "LYRASIS Reads" on Add library screen 2023-09-02 03:46:35 INFO - Button 'Search' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 03:46:36 INFO - Text Field 'Search' :: Clearing 2023-09-02 03:46:36 INFO - Text Field 'Search' :: Typing 'LYRASIS Reads' 2023-09-02 03:46:39 INFO - Button 'LYRASIS Reads' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 03:46:39 INFO - Step 5 - Account "LYRASIS Reads" is present on Accounts screen 2023-09-02 03:46:39 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 03:46:41 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 03:46:41 INFO - Button 'Accounts' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 03:46:43 INFO - Step 6 - Enter credentials for 'LYRASIS Reads' account 2023-09-02 03:46:43 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 03:46:43 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 03:46:44 INFO - Button 'Accounts' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 03:46:45 INFO - Button 'LYRASIS Reads' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 03:46:45 INFO - Locking credential with barcode 01230000000005 2023-09-02 03:46:45 INFO - There are books on the account: 2023-09-02 03:46:47 INFO - Books without revoke in link. BookName: Milk and Honey Distributor: framework.utilities.returningBooksUtil.Distributor@3369c42e 2023-09-02 03:46:47 INFO - bookName: Fahrenheit 451 Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-02 03:46:47 INFO - bookName: The Will to Change Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-02 03:46:47 INFO - bookName: Animal Instinct Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-02 03:46:47 INFO - Books without revoke in link. BookName: The Sympathizer Distributor: framework.utilities.returningBooksUtil.Distributor@444f7643 2023-09-02 03:46:47 INFO - bookName: Alice's Adventures in Wonderland Distributor: Palace Marketplace 2023-09-02 03:46:47 INFO - Books without revoke in link. BookName: The Sentence Distributor: framework.utilities.returningBooksUtil.Distributor@7cfc6da1 2023-09-02 03:46:47 INFO - Books without revoke in link. BookName: The Song of Achilles Distributor: framework.utilities.returningBooksUtil.Distributor@249ff8c2 2023-09-02 03:46:47 INFO - Count of books on the account after opening account: 4 2023-09-02 03:46:47 INFO - Text Field 'Card' :: Clearing 2023-09-02 03:46:47 INFO - Text Field 'Card' :: Typing '01230000000005' 2023-09-02 03:46:48 INFO - Text Field 'Pin' :: Clearing 2023-09-02 03:46:48 INFO - Text Field 'Pin' :: Typing '********' 2023-09-02 03:46:50 INFO - Button 'Log in' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 03:46:56 INFO - Button 'Log ... action' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-02 03:46:56 INFO - Step 7 - Login is performed successfully 2023-09-02 03:47:17 INFO - Button 'Log ... action' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-02 03:47:17 INFO - Step 8 - Open Catalog 2023-09-02 03:47:17 INFO - Button 'tabCatalog' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 03:47:38 INFO - Step 9 - Open search modal 2023-09-02 03:47:58 INFO - Button 'Search' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 03:48:00 INFO - Step 10 - Search 'available' book of distributor 'Axis 360' and bookType 'EBOOK' from "LYRASIS Reads" and save as 'bookNameInfo' 2023-09-02 03:48:00 INFO - Count of attempts to get random book name without bad symbols-1 2023-09-02 03:48:00 INFO - randomBookName: A Spark of Light 2023-09-02 03:48:00 INFO - Error details button is not present 2023-09-02 03:48:00 INFO - Text Field 'Search value input' :: Sending keys 'A Spark of Light' 2023-09-02 03:48:03 INFO - Error details button is not present 2023-09-02 03:48:06 INFO - Step 11 - Click GET action button on EBOOK book with 'bookNameInfo' bookName on catalog books screen and save book as 'bookInfo' 2023-09-02 03:48:06 INFO - Label 'lblAuthor' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-02 03:48:07 INFO - Button 'actionButton' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 03:48:13 INFO - Step 12 - Open EBOOK book with READ action button and 'bookNameInfo' bookName on catalog books screen and save book as 'bookInfo' 2023-09-02 03:48:13 INFO - Label 'lblAuthor' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-02 03:48:14 INFO - Label 'lblBookName' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 03:48:14 INFO - Step 13 - Click READ action button on book details screen 2023-09-02 03:48:16 INFO - Button 'Read' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 03:48:16 INFO - Step 14 - Scroll page forward from 7 to 9 times 2023-09-02 03:48:16 INFO - Scrolling 7 times on reader epub screen 2023-09-02 03:48:30 INFO - Step 15 - Save font size as 'fontSize' 2023-09-02 03:48:30 INFO - context - NATIVE_APP 2023-09-02 03:48:30 INFO - context - WEBVIEW_org.thepalaceproject.palace 2023-09-02 03:48:31 INFO - pageSourceWithSettingsStart+++++++++++++++++++++++++ 2023-09-02 03:48:31 INFO -

Chapter One

I walked in to see Gavin strung up in the center of the room, naked. He could smell my emotions, so I couldn’t let even an ounce of doubt into my psyche. I focused on my righteous anger — generally not a healthy place to put your energy, but it would have to do for now. Gavin had raped my mind. He deserved to have his mind raped. I had a right to be pissed.

The playroom equipment in the coterie house was built to hold the strongest vampire, so there was no doubt the shackles, spreader bars, and chains would hold the ancient, surly, sexy-as-sin bloodsucker. With a long spreader bar between his ankle shackles, another between his wrists, and chains leading to the ceiling and floor stretching him taut, he could hide nothing.

I needed him to feel vulnerable. Open. No place to hide.

I’d requested one of the big, comfortable arm chairs upstairs be brought down and put before Gavin, and I let my heels click across the floor on my way to it. I sat as if I were in my office, about to begin a session with a client.

Cora walked the room before taking her spot near the door. A nod let me know she’d checked for electronic monitoring devices and we were clear.

I looked at the vampire and held his gaze. “Tell me about the woman who turned you.”

Gavin glared at me.

“I’m guessing it was a woman. Was it a man?”

Nothing.

“Incidentally, I asked Abbott to pay my standard therapist fees for the night. Anything you tell me is protected by doctor-patient privilege. My guards have all signed non-disclosure agreements, so they can’t share information they overhear, which means Cora can’t tell what she hears, either.”

I glanced at Cora, who stood just inside the door with her arms crossed. Gavin could feel her but couldn’t see her. His Master had ordered him to stay out of our heads, but I still worried he’d take us over. My shields were stronger with Cora close, but this meant he’d hurt us both if he tore into my head again.

I’d never get through the night if I focused on the possibility though, so I kept going.

Since Gavin has a thing for natural fabrics, I’d worn a silk blouse with heavy, silky rayon dress pants and suit jacket. My hair was in a French twist, though I’d debated far longer than was probably healthy about how to wear it. I was approaching this first part of the evening as a therapist, so I’d look the part.

Now, I crossed my legs and noted the way his body tensed. His dick was soft, but my instincts told me not to mess with him sexually. Today was about making sure Gavin feared and respected me enough to never risk earning my wrath again, but it was also about fixing our relationship. This powerful vampire hated me and wanted to get rid of me — I needed to assure him I wasn’t a threat to Abbott while convincing him he didn’t want to mess with me or mine ever again.

I keyed into his aura and tried to find his vibration. His frequency. It seemed all over the place, though I could sense the walls he had up.

“You’ve learned things about me. Private things. Personal shit. Tell me about the vampire who turned you.”

Still nothing.

“Tell me about your mother.”

The flash of emotions across his face told me I’d hit the motherload. So to speak.

“Tell me.” I let it be an order with a hint of a threat.

He shook his head, but he met my gaze and finally spoke. “I was born in Dacia — now known as Romania. My father grew ill and died when I was seven. I had four siblings, and my mother couldn’t feed us without…” He stopped, started again. “It was better to sacrifice one child than to watch them all starve. She sold me into slavery when I was eight. The man who bought me liked boys. He kept me until I was probably twelve or thirteen — I lost track of the years once I was a slave. The first man who owned me had his moments of cruelty, but most of the time he was kind. So long as I complied and… performed as he expected, life wasn’t terrible.”

A single-shouldered shrug, but he continued without any prodding. “My next owner liked teens. I refused to call him daddy. I held out five days before he broke me. I’m certain he enjoyed torturing me, and I’m just as certain he remembered it fondly every time he heard the word daddy come from my lips in the following years. He kept me perhaps three years before I grew too old for his tastes, and he sold me to a brothel. Dacia and Greece share a lot in their…” A sigh, and his eyes remained focused on a spot over my head. “I was fucked by a lot of men at the brothel. I wasn’t with a woman while with my first two owners — I never had the chance. I fell in love with a whore-slave close to my age within weeks of being sold to the brothel. We were caught fucking and punished. We didn’t own our sexuality and were supposed to keep it available for paying customers.”

He met my gaze again, his eyes hard, his expressionless face a wall of granite.

“It was a long time ago,” I said. “You’re pissed at me for making you remember, but you’re only giving me the bare basics. Did you ever see your mother again?”

“I did not.”

“You didn’t go looking for her after you were a vampire?”

“The Master Vampire who turned me did so because he wanted to add me to his personal collection. He hired me out when he grew tired of me, recalled me when he wished for my company. I was a sex slave for another couple of hundred years. My mother was long-dead before I was in control of my destiny.”

“Your mother had black hair? Like you?”

The muscles of his jaw flexed. “Leave her out of this.”

“No. Was she pretty?”

His gaze bored into me but he must’ve realized he was giving too much away, and he focused somewhere over my head again, his face impassive. “My parents were peasants. Stocky. Strong. Practical. Peasants aren’t beautiful.”

“You’re their son, and you’re one of the most beautiful men I’ve ever seen.”

“If we’re just going to talk, let me out of the shackles.” A hint of annoyance in his tone, a flash of anger in his eyes. The wall was cracking.

“No, and don’t pretend you don’t know you’re beautiful. I’m guessing it’s why she sold you instead of your siblings? She could get the most money for you? Practical in all matters.”

“She did what she had to.” He wanted me to see the granite wall, but I could sense the care he was taking to look unemotional.

“Did she? Was there a way for her to whore herself out, instead of her son?”

He looked above me again, his eyes unfocused. My gut told me he was telepathing with Abbott, and I said, “No. Focus on me. Stay in the room. With me.”

He closed his eyes. “Abbott is insisting I answer your questions, and reminds me I promised him I would accept punishment from you instead of him. Do what you will, but stop this incessant talking.”

“Abbott, I know you’re listening, and that’s fine, but this is between me and Gavin. I’m respectfully asking you to stop talking to him. Cut him off so he only has me to talk to.”

Gavin gave me the tiniest of nods, and I had a feeling it was Abbott making it happen.

I repeated my last question. “Was there a way for your mother to whore herself out, instead of selling her son and turning him into one?”

His entire body seemed to tense. A livewire. He focused over my head again but answered me this time. “She wasn’t attractive. I’m not certain she’d have brought in enough money to feed us all. For sure, she’d have had to leave us alone at night. Every night.”

“You’ve talked this out with someone already? Came to terms with it?”

A vicious laugh, and when he met my gaze this time, it was with a mocking, contemptuous look. “Talking is bullshit. She did what she had to. My suffering allowed my siblings to have a roof over their heads and food in their bellies. I’ve done much worse to those I loved in order to save…” He closed his eyes a few seconds, and focused over my head again when they opened. “Before she sold me, we were freezing from lack of fuel for heat, and starving because we couldn’t afford food. I knew what she was rescuing my siblings from because I lived it along with them. Once she sold me, I was warm and had food. Life as a slave was harsh, but I was never again in danger of freezing or starving to death.”

“How did you escape the man who turned you into a vampire?”

“I killed him.” No anger now. Gavin’s voice was silky, soft. He wanted to shock me, scare me. I crossed my legs the other direction without looking away from his piercing gaze.

“Tell me about how he turned you. Did you know ahead of time? How were you prepared?”

“Prepared? You can’t prepare a human for what’s ahead of him before you sell him to a sadistic damned vampire. I was a fuck-and-feed whore in his brothel for years before he decided he didn’t want me to age beyond…” A shrug. “This.”

I took a fresh look, observing the body without considering the man who inhabited it. If Gavin didn’t look so hard — so weary of life and pissed at the universe — he probably could’ve pulled off a surly eighteen-year-old. However, I’d assumed early-to-mid-twenties the first time I’d met him. I didn’t ask how old he was when turned — he’d already told me he’d lost track of the years once becoming a slave. There were no birth certificates back then.

“Did you want to be turned?”

His tone and look were acidic. “Right, because eternity as a slave sounded like a wonderful idea.”

“You wanted death?”

Nothing.

I kept my voice soft. “Why are we here, Gavin?”

The muscles in his jaws and temple flexed. “I wanted escape. Death was the only escape I could imagine. I tried to kill myself before being returned to a particularly sadistic Duke — and was severely punished. After, there was never an opportunity to kill myself. No knives, a windowless room so I couldn’t jump. Old age was my only chance of escape.”

“They taunted you with it?”

“Don’t ask stupid questions. Of course they did.” His voice was a whip this time. Good.

I kept plugging away — questioning, demanding answers until I’d heard the whole sordid story of Gavin being used sexually almost nonstop during the week they prepared to turn him, and then finally undertook the horrible, unbearable, unescapable deed.

He was with his Master nearly two hundred years. Watching, learning, growing. Gavin hid his power and acted daft, but he made us of his Master’s extensive library and educated himself in secret.

I’m certain Abbott listened to the whole thing, but he didn’t interfere again. Several times, I had to resort to my therapist’s tricks to keep Gavin talking, but that was okay. This was between me and Gavin.

Cora stood at the door — the perfect guard. Unmoving and unnoticed, but her presence steadied me.

I learned Gavin had been a Master Vampire a few times. He’d been the kind of Master the man who’d enslaved him had been, the first time. Later, he tried to be nice, and then turned cruel when he realized his people were taking advantage of his good nature.

He’d ruled his territory through fear and torture when Abbott had moved into the lands adjoining his and made him an offer. Gavin felt the new vampire’s power and could’ve never hoped to defeat him. Abbott could’ve easily taken Gavin’s territory but had instead offered to join their demesnes and make Gavin his second.

He’d refused at first. Never would he put himself at another’s mercy again — even if it meant true death.

However, Abbott had nurtured their relationship instead of attacking. Gavin had met the other vampires in Abbott’s coterie, and he’d eventually agreed to Abbott’s offer — and he’d been accepted into the fold with respect and caring. Abbott had given Gavin a home for the first time since before his father had died. He didn’t say it, but I could hear it in his voice — Gavin had been alone and cold for centuries, and Abbott had shown him how to love again.

Abbott was the father Gavin had needed. Abbott had saved him, and Gavin would do anything for the Master Vampire. Even go against his wishes to try to keep him safe.

It took hours for me to feel I understood Gavin, and once I did, I regretted what I’d have to do next.

2023-09-02 03:48:31 INFO - pageSourceWithSettingsEnd+++++++++++++++++++++++++ 2023-09-02 03:48:32 INFO - Taking screenshot 2023-09-02 03:48:33 INFO - Test finished - logging out 2023-09-02 03:48:34 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 03:48:36 INFO - Button 'tabSettings' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 03:48:37 INFO - Button 'Accounts' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 03:48:38 INFO - Button 'LYRASIS Reads' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 03:48:40 INFO - Text Field 'Card' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-02 03:48:40 INFO - Text Field 'Pin' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-02 03:48:41 INFO - Button 'Log out' :: Clicking 2023-09-02 03:49:01 INFO - Button 'Log in' :: Getting text from element 2023-09-02 03:49:02 INFO - Unlocking credential for current thread 2023-09-02 03:49:02 INFO - isLoggerNullAfterAnnotation-framework.utilities.Logger@1684cb30